[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What can you tell me about that part of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "that", "part", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Well, there are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "I believe we're working on the assumption that it's by the Tsarnaev family, possibly an uncle, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "believe", "we", "'re", "working", "on", "the", "assumption", "that", "it", "'s", "by", "the", "Tsarnaev", "family", ",", "possibly", "an", "uncle", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, that is one of the possibilities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "one", "of", "the", "possibilities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tsarnaev"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Or do you fear it's something linked to Dagestan, to extremists in a wider circle of dangerous people?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "fear", "it", "'s", "something", "linked", "to", "Dagestan", ",", "to", "extremists", "in", "a", "wider", "circle", "of", "dangerous", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, first of all, it certainly could be what you described.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "certainly", "could", "be", "what", "you", "described", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dagestan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How do you deal with this new menace of young people who haven't picked up on many radars before, doing this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "this", "new", "menace", "of", "young", "people", "who", "have", "n't", "picked", "up", "on", "many", "radars", "before", ",", "doing", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Do you think they're right to level that kind of criticism?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "they", "'re", "right", "to", "level", "that", "kind", "of", "criticism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I think at least to a limited degree that the criticism is warranted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "at", "least", "to", "a", "limited", "degree", "that", "the", "criticism", "is", "warranted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Is that a good move for America, do you think, to do something of that nature?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "good", "move", "for", "America", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "do", "something", "of", "that", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "My personal opinion, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "personal", "opinion", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "But if it turns out there is unequivocal evidence of sarin use, that they have used weapons of mass destruction, chemical weapons and so on, Obama, having said that that's the red line, would have to do something, wouldn't he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "it", "turns", "out", "there", "is", "unequivocal", "evidence", "of", "sarin", "use", ",", "that", "they", "have", "used", "weapons", "of", "mass", "destruction", ",", "chemical", "weapons", "and", "so", "on", ",", "Obama", ",", "having", "said", "that", "that", "'s", "the", "red", "line", ",", "would", "have", "to", "do", "something", ",", "would", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I don't know if he would have to do something.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "he", "would", "have", "to", "do", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Or do you feel like they're getting it under control?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "they", "'re", "getting", "it", "under", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, I don't have much experience with fire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "much", "experience", "with", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Or is there a fear that other houses are coming into its radar?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "there", "a", "fear", "that", "other", "houses", "are", "coming", "into", "its", "radar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "If you're asking me what's going on surrounding, the wind I know has been somewhat swirling today.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "asking", "me", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "surrounding", ",", "the", "wind", "I", "know", "has", "been", "somewhat", "swirling", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "I mean, do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "At the time I did.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "the", "time", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Now that she's turned up alive, do you know what the legal position is with your second marriage?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "that", "she", "'s", "turned", "up", "alive", ",", "do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "legal", "position", "is", "with", "your", "second", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "I mean, do you -- do you want to see her?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "As of right now I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "of", "right", "now", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Morgan, what was your reaction when you saw the new picture of your mother?", "question_tokens": ["Morgan", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "new", "picture", "of", "your", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "It's definitely hard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "definitely", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "PRP$", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Or do you think it's beyond any redemption or apology?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "beyond", "any", "redemption", "or", "apology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I hope to eventually forgive her one day for myself, not for her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "to", "eventually", "forgive", "her", "one", "day", "for", "myself", ",", "not", "for", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "How did you feel when you heard what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "heard", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I was really shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "really", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "How would you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "I'm now being arrested and handcuffed?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "now", "being", "arrested", "and", "handcuffed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Do you know my name, sir?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "my", "name", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I don't need to know your name.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "your", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "You don't need to know my name?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "my", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Not quite yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "quite", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "The marketing is directed at the parents, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "marketing", "is", "directed", "at", "the", "parents", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Should it be banned, that kind of advertising?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "it", "be", "banned", ",", "that", "kind", "of", "advertising", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I think that there's an argument to be made in favor of that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "an", "argument", "to", "be", "made", "in", "favor", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "We should focus on the central problem then?", "question_tokens": ["We", "should", "focus", "on", "the", "central", "problem", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "We can.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "But you agree with me, then, that you would bring in a form of gun control, which would be prohibiting companies like Crickett from targeting young people with guns?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "agree", "with", "me", ",", "then", ",", "that", "you", "would", "bring", "in", "a", "form", "of", "gun", "control", ",", "which", "would", "be", "prohibiting", "companies", "like", "Crickett", "from", "targeting", "young", "people", "with", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I'm fairly certain the liability law already covers a lot of this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "fairly", "certain", "the", "liability", "law", "already", "covers", "a", "lot", "of", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What is going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, they're not effective, unfortunately.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "effective", ",", "unfortunately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Because that is the fundamental basis of American freedom.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "is", "the", "fundamental", "basis", "of", "American", "freedom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Where would the tyranny come from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "the", "tyranny", "come", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "The tyranny would come from the government.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "tyranny", "would", "come", "from", "the", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Barack Obama's government?", "question_tokens": ["Barack", "Obama", "'s", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "No, not Barack Obama's government.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "Barack", "Obama", "'s", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "So whose government?", "question_tokens": ["So", "whose", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I couldn't name you a name.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "n't", "name", "you", "a", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "You personally believe, like a third of these people, that you will need in the next few years, it says -- you will need to have weapons to take on your own government?", "question_tokens": ["You", "personally", "believe", ",", "like", "a", "third", "of", "these", "people", ",", "that", "you", "will", "need", "in", "the", "next", "few", "years", ",", "it", "says", "--", "you", "will", "need", "to", "have", "weapons", "to", "take", "on", "your", "own", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I don't believe in the next few years.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "in", "the", "next", "few", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Why don't we just go with a full gun ban?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "we", "just", "go", "with", "a", "full", "gun", "ban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "We've discussed this.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "discussed", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What such a cheap shot against a guy who did a pretty brave thing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "such", "a", "cheap", "shot", "against", "a", "guy", "who", "did", "a", "pretty", "brave", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I don't think it's a cheap shot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "cheap", "shot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", ":"], "qSentId": 478, "question": "I think you may be homophobic simply because you said why is Jason Collins a hero because he's gay?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "may", "be", "homophobic", "simply", "because", "you", "said", "why", "is", "Jason", "Collins", "a", "hero", "because", "he", "'s", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I don't understand why --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "understand", "why", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Collins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why sneer at a guy for coming out?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "sneer", "at", "a", "guy", "for", "coming", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I'm not sneering at him --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sneering", "at", "him", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "-- one thing homophobic?", "question_tokens": ["--", "one", "thing", "homophobic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I don't think it's homophobic to simply say we're apathetic about people's personal lives.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "homophobic", "to", "simply", "say", "we", "'re", "apathetic", "about", "people", "'s", "personal", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Come off it?", "question_tokens": ["Come", "off", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Got to leave it there, but come off it.", "answer_tokens": ["Got", "to", "leave", "it", "there", ",", "but", "come", "off", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Shapiro"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Why is it a big deal?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "a", "big", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Ben Shapiro, come back soon on the Grill there, and well roasted he was, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Ben", "Shapiro", ",", "come", "back", "soon", "on", "the", "Grill", "there", ",", "and", "well", "roasted", "he", "was", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "I'm now being arrested and handcuffed?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "now", "being", "arrested", "and", "handcuffed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Do you know my name, sir?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "my", "name", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I don't need to know your name.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "your", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "You don't need to know my name?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "my", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Not quite yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "quite", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last weekend"], "PERSON": ["Reese Witherspoon"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "How bad is this for Reese Witherspoon?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "is", "this", "for", "Reese", "Witherspoon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, we've seen Reese Witherspoon taking on these kind of darker rolls, this much more complicated roll in \"Mud,\" which came out last weekend.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ve", "seen", "Reese", "Witherspoon", "taking", "on", "these", "kind", "of", "darker", "rolls", ",", "this", "much", "more", "complicated", "roll", "in", "``", "Mud", ",", "''", "which", "came", "out", "last", "weekend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reese Witherspoon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Abby, sincere enough for you?", "question_tokens": ["Abby", ",", "sincere", "enough", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "She has got to be so humiliated.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "has", "got", "to", "be", "so", "humiliated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "I don't think I can do this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "can", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "It's easy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex. Here"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Or was it just plain offensive?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "it", "just", "plain", "offensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "I'm going to go with racist for 500, Alex. Here's the thing, it can be satirical, it can be witty and it can be edgy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "with", "racist", "for", "500", ",", "Alex.", "Here", "'s", "the", "thing", ",", "it", "can", "be", "satirical", ",", "it", "can", "be", "witty", "and", "it", "can", "be", "edgy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Abby, you go?", "question_tokens": ["Abby", ",", "you", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I was saying, it's completely misogynistic as well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "saying", ",", "it", "'s", "completely", "misogynistic", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Maeve, you're as incensed as Abby?", "question_tokens": ["Maeve", ",", "you", "'re", "as", "incensed", "as", "Abby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I think the fact that we're even talking about this illustrates that it may have very well been meant to just go viral and be pulled.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "'re", "even", "talking", "about", "this", "illustrates", "that", "it", "may", "have", "very", "well", "been", "meant", "to", "just", "go", "viral", "and", "be", "pulled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Why else would we be talking about Mountain Dew, right?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "else", "would", "we", "be", "talking", "about", "Mountain", "Dew", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "The other thing we're talking about today is Mitt Romney has made this commencement speech today.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "other", "thing", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "today", "is", "Mitt", "Romney", "has", "made", "this", "commencement", "speech", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Is it a good idea for women to have lots of kids very quickly and then go off and do what they want to do?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "good", "idea", "for", "women", "to", "have", "lots", "of", "kids", "very", "quickly", "and", "then", "go", "off", "and", "do", "what", "they", "want", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I think we are just seeing the real Mitt Romney emerge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "are", "just", "seeing", "the", "real", "Mitt", "Romney", "emerge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "130502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Marc, final word from you?", "question_tokens": ["Marc", ",", "final", "word", "from", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "This is the Mitt Romney that I didn't want to vote for and that I didn't vote for.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "Mitt", "Romney", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "vote", "for", "and", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "vote", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]